

CONTACT

- +8801748298776 +8801620833383
- asifimtiyajchowdhury@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-asifimtiyaj-chowdhury-7945a11b3/
- f facebook.com/asif.niloy.714/
- https://github.com/asifichy
-) https://twitter.com/HelloChowdhury
- (h) https://www.hackerrank.com/asifimtiyaj
- Subject to blogger.com/u/2/blog/posts/7393187492704 601641?pli=1
- ☐ https://asifimtiyajchowdhuryportfolio.netlify.app/
- House-41, Block-E, Road-01, Bonosree, Rampura, Dhaka-1219

EDUCATION

Bachelor in Computer Science and Engineering

East West University

CGPA: 3.08 out of 4.00 2019-2023

Higher Secondary Certificate

(Major: Science)

Birshrestho Munshi Abdur Rouf

Public College

GPA: 4.08 out of 5.00

2019

Secondary School Certificate

(Major: Science)

Ideal School and College

GPA: 5.00 out of 5.00

2017

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth: July 28, 2001 Marital Status: Married Nationality: Bangladeshi National ID No: 7365060438 Passport ID No: A02213237

LANGUAGE

Bengali

English

MD. ASIF IMTIYAJ CHOWDHURY

Software Engineer

PROFILE

"To be a part of a dynamic, progressive organization that will provide me the opportunity to grow professionally while utilizing my skills and experience in the area to add value to the organization. Along with being a software engineer and working with all of my passion, my life's goal is to be a good person."

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C, C++, Java, Python, PHP, JavaScript

DATABASE

MySQL, SQLite, Oracle SQL, MongoDB

MOBILE APPLICATION DEVELOPMENT

- Android
- Flutter

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Bootstrap

SOFTWARE QUALITY TESTING

• Selenium (w/Python)

CLOUD SERVICES AND

TECHNOLOGIES

- Huawei Cloud
- Amazon Web Services
- Linux
- Docker
- Kubernetes

SCIENTIFIC RESEARCH

- IoT Based semi-automated robot for cleaning
- E-waste management

WORK EXPERIENCE

CLOUD ENGINEER INTERN HUAWEI TECHNOLOGIES BANGLADESH

2024 - Present

- Huawei Cloud
 - Robi Datathon 3.0 (worked as a solution architect)
 - Deployed websites on CCE with Docker
- Amazon Web Services

SOFTWARE ENGINEER (WEB) INTERN

2024- Present

HEXEN

- Web Development
 - Front-end Development
 - HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, ReactJS, TailwindCSS
 - Backend Development
 - NodeJS, MongoDB, EspressJS

EXPERTISE

- Strong Leadership
- Team Player
- Research Collaboraiton
- Problem solving attitude
- Seamless Communication
- Time Management

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- MS Word
- MS PowerPoint
- MS Excel
- Data Entry

REFERENCES

Dr. Md. Hasanul Ferdaus

Assistant Professor
East West University
Department of Computer
Science & Engineering
Phone: +8801799-687213

Email: hasanul.ferdaus@ewubd.edu

Dr. Md. Zillur Rahman Khan

Associate Professor and Head Dept. of Psychiatry Shaheed Suhrawardy Medical College, Dhaka Phone: +8801716906520 Email: mzrkhan@gmail.com